

Excellent technical aptitude Experienced working with Core Java, Collections & Design Patterns. Proficient in technologies such as Spring Framework, Spring MVC, Spring AOP, Spring Security, Hibernate, JSP, Servlet, Web Services, SQL.



Current Designation: Software Engineer 1 Total Experience: 2 Year(s) 7 Month(s)

Current Company: Bentley Systems Notice Period: 1 Month

Current Location: Pune Highest Degree: PG Diploma [Computers]

Pref. Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore, Mumbai, Pune
Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: Software Engineer 1, Software Development, Software Application Development, Backend

Development, Data Structure, Spring MVC, Core Java, Hibernate, OOPS, Servlet, GIT, SQL, JSP, Servlets, Java, Spring

Security, Spring Framework

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 22-Jan-21 Last Modified: 22-Jan-21

Summary

Software Engineer with 2+ years of experience focused on backend development

Other Skills: Software Development, Software Application Development, Project Management, Requirement Gathering, Backend Development, Data Structure, Spring MVC, Core Java, Spring Core, Hibernate, OOPS, Servlet, GIT, SQL, JSP

Work Experience

Bentley Systems as Software Engineer 1

Jun 2018 to Till Date

Software Engineer 1 Bentley Systems

06/2020 - Present, Pune

Developing plugins to convert the unified format data into suitable repository Native API data.

Associate Software Engineer

Bentley Systems

06/2018 - 06/2020, Pune

Worked on SQL Server to define stored procedures and triggers for business requirements. Worked with Azure Data Factory(ADF) to Migrated SQL databases from servers to Azure.

Worked with U-SQL to transform unstructured data into structured data. Integrate the project with the Log Dispatcher service. Used singleton pattern.

Create a common service access library with JAVA for authorization and endpoint access.

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Computer Science) from SWAMI KESHVANAND INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY in 2017

PG: PG Diploma (Computers) from Centre for Development of Advanced Computing (CDAC) in 2018

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience
Data Structure, Spring MVC, Core Java			
Spring Core, Hibernate, OOPS, Servlet, GIT			
SQL,JSP			

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English	Expert			
Hindi	Expert			

Projects

Project Title: E- Panchayat Tender Management System

Client: Academic Assignments Nature of Employment: Full Time

Duration: Jan 2018 - Jan 2018 Onsite / Offsite: Offsite

Project Details: Developed an application that allows a user to access either as panchayat or as a contractor and they can view the tender content as per their authorization and also introduced an admin feature to monitor the activity on the application.

The technology used - Spring MVC, Hibernate, JSP, MySQL.

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

Physically Challenged: No

Job Type: Permanent

Employment Status: Full time